A Guide to the Drew family papers, 1891-1981
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Drew family papers, 1891-1981
Library of Virginia
54078
1.575 cubic feet (4 boxes).
Drew family
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Purchased
Biographical Information
Annie Spratley Jarratt was born 21 April 1876 in Greensville County, Virginia, to Benjamin Franklin Drew (1839-1913) and Julia Ann Nicholson Jarratt (1847-1920). She married Benjamin Clinton Drew (1869-1910) 31 October 1906 and they resided in Wakefield, Sussex County. Annie Jarratt Drew died 16 August 1935. Julia Emily Drew was born 11 December 1907 in Wakefield, Sussex County, to Annie Drew Jarratt and Benjamin Clinton Drew. She graduated from Blackstone College for Girls and from the State Teachers College in Farmville, Virginia. She married Joseph Langhorne Francis (1904-1968) 20 June 1942, and they had one son, Langhorne Drew Francis (1943-2002). Julia Emily Drew Francis died 6 July 1986. Ann Clinton Drew was born to Annie Jarratt Drew and Benjamin Clinton Drew 5 February 1910 in Wakefield. She graduated from the State Teachers College also and taught in Sussex County Schools. Ann Clinton Drew died 3 October 1997.
Scope and Content
Papers, 1891-1981, of the Drew family of Wakefield, Sussex County, and Richmond, Virginia, consisting of letters, as well as greeting cards, deeds, financial records, and invitations, documenting the lives of Annie Spratley Jarratt Drew (1876-1935), Julia Emily Drew Francis (1907-1986), and Ann Clinton Drew (1910-1997), as well as relatives and friends; and detailing life in Sussex County.
Contents List
- Letters, 1891-1900 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Letters, 1901, 1903 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Letters, 1904-1905 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Letters, May-September 1906 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Letters, October 1906 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Letters, December 1906 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Letters, 1908-1909 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Letters, 1910 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Letters, 1911-1917 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Letters, 1919-1920 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Envelopes, empty, 1910s (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Letters, 2-4 Februry 1921 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Letters, 7-8 February 1921 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Letters, 9-13 February 1921 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Letters, 14-18 February 1921 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Letters, 22-25 February 1921 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Letters, [February-March] 1921 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Letters, 1-4 March 1921 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Letters, 7-9 March 1921 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Letters, 10-12, 25 March 1921 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Letters, May-December 1921 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Letters, 1922-1924 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Letters, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Julia Emily Drew report cards from Blackstone College for Girls, 1925-1927 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Letters, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Letters, May-10 December 1927 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Letters, 21-24 December 1927 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Julia Emily Drew report cards from State Teachers College, 1927-1930 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Letters, January-August 1928 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Letters, December 1928 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Letters, March-19 December 1929 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Letters, 20-21 December 1929 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Letters, 22-25 December 1929 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Letters, 1930 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- John N. Jarratt application for license, 1930 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Christmas cards, ca. 1920s (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Letters, January-May 1931 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Letters, June-December 1931 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Letters, 1932-1934 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Letters, February-June 1935 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Letters, August-December 1935 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Deed from Irvin E. Francis to J. L. Francis, 20 May 1935 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Letters, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Letters, 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Letters, February-June 1942 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Letters, July-December 1942 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Letters, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Letters, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Letters, 1945, 1947, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Deed from Gertrude Jarratt to Blanche R. Jarratt, et. als., 29 October 1949 (recorded 5 January 1950) (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Letters, 1952-1960 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Letters, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Letters, January-June 1962 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Letters, August-September 1962 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Letters, 1964, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Letters, 1967-1970 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Letters, 1972-1973, 1979, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Letters to Julia Emily Drew and Ann C. Drew, from Julia Emily Drew, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Postcards to Annie J. Drew, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Letters from Elizabeth J. White, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Letters to various recipients and unidentified, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Christmas cards and birthday cards to the Drew family, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Julia A. Jarratt estate financial records, 1924-1955 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous papers, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)